Mayank Uppal



muppal88@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mayankuppal



https://www.mayankuppal.com

Summary

A tech enthusiast who keeps an eye for the designs and products around himself.

Love to research, analyze and brainstorm on the products and get them delivered through beautiful design approaches keeping the industry standards in mind.

In a short span of 2 years, I have gained experience in different domains, Here's an insight:

- Worked on more than 40 Websites and Landing Pages
- Designed more than half a dozen fully functional Apps, which have an amazing ROI
- Conceptualized and Worked on 5+ SaaS products

Experience

User Experience Designer

Appinventiv

Mar 2021 - Present (1 year +)

Worked on Different Projects and Different client domains from SaaS to Social Media and many others.

Created many Web and Mobile Designs from scratch including Wireframes and Prototypes using different technologies and software like Adobe XD, Figma, InVision, and Balsamiq.

C UI Designer

Gensofts Infosolutions Pvt. Ltd.

Feb 2021 - Mar 2021 (2 months)

- Worked on designing a website daily for clients.
- Participating in different website design competitions
- Creating Landing PAges, SaaS Dashboards and Others



Lead User Experience Designer

mauka®

Oct 2020 - Jan 2021 (4 months)

- Redesigned the product from scratch using Different tools for an audience of Tier-2 and Tier-3 Cities.
- Kept an eye on User Experience and Creating Personas
- Did UX Testing to increase the ROI



User Experience Designer

Concevoir Web Services Pvt. Ltd.

Jul 2020 - Sep 2020 (3 months)

Interned in this position to work for international clients, where I designed and revamped many websites and landing pages for them

user Experience Designer

mauka®

Mar 2020 - Jul 2020 (5 months)

- Designed the product from scratch using Different tools for an audience of Tier-2 and Tier-3 Cities.
- Kept an eye on User Experience and Creating Personas

User Experience Designer

Solve Foundation Feb 2020 - Apr 2020 (3 months)

Education

HMR Institute of Technology and Management

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science 2017 - 2021

Arwachin Bharti Bhawan Sr. Sec. School

2010 - 2017

Dr. Tobgyel School, Bhutan

2009 - 2010

Skills

User Interface Design • Entrepreneurship • User Experience (UX) • Python (Programming Language) • Web Design • Wireframing • Product Design • Adobe XD • User Experience Design (UED)